Hello.
こんにちは
Are you nervous?
緊張してます?
I know.
知ってます
You know.
知ってますね
Your voice seems hoarse.
声かすれそうですよね
Are you nervous?
緊張してます?
I felt like it was quite dignified,
結構堂々としてる感じがしたんですけど、
I was nervous inside.
内心が緊張してたんですね
Do you know what we're going to do today?
今日何するかって知ってます?
Yeah.
うん
What, you don't know?
え、知らない?
I know.
知ってます
You know that, right?
知ってますよね
It would be a shame if you didn't know.
知らなかったらやばいね
What are you doing today?
今日何するんですか?
picture?
え?
If you don't know anything, the old man will get caught in a passive sexual relationship.
何も分かってないと、おじさんが不動意性交渉に捕まっちゃうん
Yes, it is.
です よ
There may be some specific content, but
具体的な中身はあるかもしれないですけど、
What are you doing today?
今日は何するんですか?
It's not something you should think about.
そんな考えるようなことじゃないですよ
It's simple and good.
シンプルでいいですよ
Like taking pictures.
撮るみたいな
I'll take a picture of you having sex.
エッチしてるところを撮っちゃいますよ
I'll regret it to the whole world, but is it okay?
全世界に後悔しちゃいますけど、大丈夫ですか?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
OK.
OKね
If you don't stay safe here, you'll get arrested.
ここはどういっといてないと捕まっちゃうんで
Are you okay.
大丈夫
It's okay.
大丈夫ね
Are you in need of money?
お金困ってるんですか?
Aren't you in trouble?
困ってない?
This is a dark part-time job.
闇バイトですよ、これ
It's a bit old, isn't it?
ちょっともう古いですかね
What should I call you today?
今日なんて呼びしたらいいですか?
Aren't you going to tell me who you look like?
誰に似てるとかって言われないの?
Please don't go to headquarters.
本部にはやめてくださいね
With Ten-chan.
天ちゃんで
Is Ten-chan okay?
天ちゃんでいいですか?
yes.
はい
How old are you?
おいくつです?
It's 21.
21です
21 years old?
21歳?
Aren't you young?
若いじゃないですか?
Life is fun now.
今、人生楽しいですね
Life is fun.
人生楽しいよ
What specifically do you enjoy?
具体的に何が楽しいですか?
love affair?
恋愛?
friend?
友達?
friend.
友達
Are you friends?
友 達 な の?
Are your friends having fun?
友達楽しい?
You'll be able to drink alcohol.
お酒とか飲めるようになりますからね
It's fun.
楽しいですね
But you need money to play.
でも遊ぶのにお金がいるからね
I'll help you.
助けてあげます
Are you going with dad?
パパと行っちゃいますか?
Let's go with dad.
パパと行っちゃいましょうね
Yes, please stand.
はい、立ってください
I'll take a thumbnail.
サ ムネ撮りますよ
Can I turn around and wait?
後ろ向いて待っていい?
Turn around.
後ろ向いて
So, can you put your hand next to me and stick your butt out?
で、そばに手ついてお尻突き出せる?
Can I eat it?
食っちゃっていいですか?
What, no?
え、ダメ?
May I?
いいですか?
Ah, two are now 20.
あ、2つ20になってんだね
Do you like black?
黒が好きなの?
I like black.
黒好き
Do you like black?
黒好きなの?
Is it closed?
閉めてる?
It's a lie, it's a lie.
嘘です、嘘
It's not closed.
閉めてない
It's easy to end here.
ここもう終わりしやすいからね
I'll take it down.
下ろしますね
Please look forward.
前向いてください
It's hot, so let's take it off.
熱いんで脱いじゃいましょうね
Please take it off.
脱いちゃってください
Can I put it there instead of the sofa?
ソファーじゃなくて、そっちの方に置ける?
That one?
そっちの方?
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
I'll take it.
取りますよ
Strender.
ストレンダー
What is your charm point about your body?
自分の体のチャームポイントはどこですか?
feet.
足
feet?
足?
Foot distance?
足距離?
Are you confident in your legs?
足自信あるの?
Is it your feet?
足ですか?
It's thin, that's for sure.
細いね、確かにね
It's Hawaii.
ハワイですね
Is this still bad?
これでも悪目ですか?
It's disgusting, isn't it?
きもいでしょ
Does anyone do this?
こんなことする人います?
The one who looks for evil eyes.
悪目探すやつ
Is this it?
これですか?
That's too perverted.
変態がすぎますね
Are you working hard on your legs?
足は何か頑張っていることあるんですか?
I'm walking.
歩いてます
Are you walking?
歩いてますか?
Will I get thinner if I walk?
歩いたら細くなるの?
Ah, yes.
あ、そう
Is it impossible?
無理ですか?
Well then, um, uh...
じゃあちょっと、えっとね、 あ、
Yes, just a moment, I'll explain.
そうだ、ちょっとね、 説明しますよ、
Pose.
ポーズを
Okay, just a little.
よ い しょっと
Can you sit like this?
こうやって座れる?
Pull your ass out like this.
こうやってお尻をね、引き出して
If Safa is getting in the way, you can just get him out of the way.
サファーが邪魔だったら、どけてもらっていいんで
Your butthole, around here?
お尻の穴、ここら辺?
Ah, is that correct?
あ、当たってる?
Can I just take the pants down on my legs?
足だけパンツ、下ろしちゃっていいですか?
Is it okay?
いいです?
There are viewers with a butt fetish.
お尻フェチのね、 視聴者さんがいるんですよ
Ah, something is a little off.
あ、ちょっとなんかめくれてますよ
I have some kind of scar.
なんか傷があります
So, I was like, can I sit like this?
で、なんかね、 こう、こう座れる?
It emphasizes your butt.
お尻が強調されるんですよ
I think it's better to spread your legs apart and stay in the middle.
足広げって、真ん中のほうがいいと思う
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
そうそうそうそう
Yes, then you can stop normally.
はい、じゃあ、普通に止まっていいですよ
Okay.
よし
What is your favorite food?
好きな食べ物は何ですか?
Yakiniku.
焼き肉
Do you like grilled meat?
焼き肉好きなの?
rare?
珍しい?
Isn't it rare?
珍しくないか?
I guess there aren't many women who don't like grilled meat.
なんかね、焼き肉苦手な女性多くないですか?
It's kind of greasy.
なんか、脂が、みたいな
Grilled meat that you can make without getting tired.
疲れずに作る焼き肉
is that so?
そうですか?
What part is it?
部位は何ですか?
abdominal body.
腹身
It's gutsy.
ガッツイだね
My legs are
足が、 お
Mr. Ji's version is completely different.
じ さんのこの、 全然違うんだけど
It's smooth.
すべつべですね
Are you losing your hair?
脱毛してるんですか?
yes.
はい
Oh, I'm taking it.
あ、取ってる
Absolutely stinky.
絶対臭い
I'm sorry.
すみませんね
The scent of goldenrod was astringent.
キンボクセイの香りが渋した
Okay.
よし
Well then, can I stand up again?
じゃあ ね、また立てばっていいですか?
It's hard to see though.
見とくさいですけど
Let's take off your bra.
ブラジャーを取っちゃいましょう
Oh, sorry.
あ、ごめん
How many cups?
何カップですか?
D
May I?
いいですか?
Please take a look.
見ちゃってください
Ah, hello.
あ、こんにちは
I was hiding for a long time.
ずっと隠れもしてたからね
It's beautiful.
綺麗ですね
It's beautiful and quite large.
綺麗で、結構、 地 首とでかいですね
It's coming out like a sore thumb.
ぼっくり出てますよ
With Cash's boobs like this, and this ugly head,
こんなキャッシュのおっぱいに、 このぼっくりな地首、
It's so dark.
どえろいですね
copper?
どう?
What do you think of this blank looking head?
このぼっくりな地首、どう?
What do you think?
どうですか?
How do you feel about being given a head that looks exactly like this?
このぼっくりな地首を授かって、 どう?
I'm a fool.
ぼっくりなんですよ
Some people are small.
小 さい人もいますからね
Such a cash-rich body, with a dimpled neck.
こんなキャッシュな体が、 ぼっくりした地首つけて
I'll take a photo.
写真撮るよ
So, can I sit and wait?
じゃあ、座って待っていい?
Can I lick it?
舐めちゃっていいですか?
Is it no good?
ダメですか?
picture?
え?
what?
何?
May I?
いいですか?
interesting.
面白い
It makes a lot of sense.
すごい意味がする
Is it okay to have a baby who drinks a lot?
めっちゃおっぱい飲む赤ちゃんとかやっていい?
It's absorbent.
吸い応えがあるね
I'm feeling prickly.
ちくりぼっくりしてる
Slowly put your back on the sofa,
ゆっくり背中をソファーにつけて、
It's really blurry though.
めっちゃぼっきりしてるんだけど
This is amazing.
すごいよ、これ
It's coming out a lot.
めちゃくちゃ出てるじゃん
Bring your hands behind your head.
両手を頭の後ろに持ってきてごらん
oh yeah.
そうそう
Bokkkuri Mabumie.
ぼっくりまぶみえ
Cut Open and cut.
カット開けてカット
That's right.
沿 ってますね
Are you following it?
沿ってるんですか?
It's closed.
閉めてる
gold wooden curtains
金木製のカーテン
I will explain.
を します
Can I lick you for a moment?
ちょっと、舐めてもいいですか?
I think it's too tight to open, so you can lower it.
開ききついと思うんで、下ろしていいですよ
Have you ever been licked completely?
バッキリ舐められたことあります?
there is?
あります?
Cake stop?
ケーキ停車?
You don't have to wash it anymore.
もう洗わなくていいからね
You can go home.
帰っていいからね
You can take that down.
そっち、下ろしていいよ
Shall I finish it?
仕上げようか
Are you holding back a bit?
ちょっと、引いてます?
Haven't you pulled it?
引いてないの?
Let's take off your pants.
タンツを脱いましょうね
Please do the same posture as before, sticking your butt out.
さっきの、お尻を突き出す姿勢をやってください
So let's take off our pants.
それで、タンツを脱いちゃいましょうね
Let's lick it.
舐めていこうね
Which way should I go?
どっちから行く?
From here.
こっちから
You're wearing pants like this.
こんなパンツ履いてるんだね
Can I have you stand?
立ってもらっていい?
I'd like you to stand normally.
普通に立ってもらっていいよ
Come here.
こ っちに来て
Please have this.
これ持ってください
Please tell me these are my pants.
これ 私のパンツですって言ってください
It's beautiful.
綺麗だね
Look here.
こっち見て
You're tall, after all.
身長高いね、今更
Is it true?
本当ですか?
Isn't it expensive?
高くないですか?
it's not?
そうではない?
Spread your legs?
足広げる?
I'm curious, bottom.
気になるよ、下
You can look down.
下見ていいよ
Become a mirror.
前 鏡になって
Well then, stretch your back now.
じゃあ、すぐに背伸ばして
Stretch your back.
背 伸ばして
Do you know what M-shaped legs are?
M字開脚って分かりますか?
So sit on the cushion,
じゃあ、クッションの上に座って、
Do the M-shaped split leg position.
M字開脚の姿勢をやってください
My eyes look good today.
今日、前目がいいね
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
And with Petan.
で、ペターンと
Can I have you stretch your legs for a moment?
一旦足伸ばしてもらっていい?
Okay.
いいわ
Do you really want to hide it?
やっぱ隠したいの?
Lay your hands on your sides.
手横にして
When I asked her to stretch her legs, she pinged.
足伸ばしてもらうと、ピーンと
Yeah, yeah, nice, nice.
そうそうそう、いいねいいね
I like the style.
スタイルいいね
Look here.
こっち見て
Get into an M-legged position.
M字開脚の姿勢になってください
Yes, put your hands behind your head.
そうそう、両手は頭の後ろに持ってきて
Don't hide anything.
何も包み隠さず
I can see everything.
ありとあらゆるものが見えちゃってますよ
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
Privacy...
プライバシーの...
There's no privacy at all.
プライバシーが全然ない
Is it Ten-chan?
天ちゃんだっけ?
I can see everything about Ten-chan.
天ちゃんのありとあらゆるものが見えちゃってますよ
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
Please tell me to look at everything about me.
私の全てを見てくださいって言ってください
Are you 21 years old?
21歳だっけ?
Please look at everything for 21 years.
21年間の全てを見てくださいって
You can push it even if it's tight with both hands.
両手きついともから押していいよ
Hey, can you spread your pussy open?
ちょっと さ、 あの、 おまんこ広げれる?
It's a beautiful color.
綺麗な色してますね
It's healthy.
健康的ですよ
Can I take a look at Cleatois?
クリートイス見ていい?
Oh, it's tiny.
あ、ちっちゃいね
Here, it's thick here.
ここね、 ここ分厚いよね
It's thick.
分厚いです
Oh, are you aware?
あ、自覚あるの?
I'm aware.
自覚ある
It's okay to cut corners.
手抜けていいよ
It's thick in here.
ここ分厚いよね
This is Brun Brun.
ブルンブルンじゃん、これ
This is thick.
これ分厚いよね
It's like lips.
唇みたい
I was going to take a bath, but I ended up taking the first photo on the bed.
お風呂行くんですけど、 最後、ベッドの上で 最初の写真撮った
Do you remember your posture?
時 の姿勢覚えてる?
Ten-chan from Flag Kambo.
旗カンボの天ちゃん
Yeah, yeah, nice, nice.
そうそうそう、 いいねいいね
Your body is beautiful.
体綺麗ですね
It looks like a sculpture.
彫刻みたいですよ
Look here.
こっち見て
Over the past 21 years, you have grown into an erotic body.
21年間、 エロい体に育ちましたね
Put your hands under your head and wait, okay?
両手をさ、頭の下に持ってきて、 待って いい?
Can I enjoy this body after this?
この体をこの後、 美味しくいただいちゃっていいですか?
Is it no good?
ダメですか?
No?
ダ メ?
good?
いい?
Shall we take a bath?
お風呂入りましょうかね
Can I take a picture of you from behind?
後ろ姿撮っていい?
Bring both hands under your head.
両手頭の下に持ってきて
Okay, let's take a bath then.
はい、じゃあお風呂入りましょうか
Thank you for your continued support today.
今日よろしくお願いしますね
Uncle, you feel bad.
おじさん気持ち悪いよね
I'm getting goosebumps.
すごい鳥肌立ってる
Uncle, you feel bad.
おじさん気持ち悪いよね
amazing.
すごい
I came to this side.
こっち側に来た
Hey.
おーい
Can I lick it?
舐めちゃっていい?
What are you thinking about?
何考え事してるの?
I haven't.
してない
You're not thinking about anything right now, are you?
今何か考え事してないでしょ
What should I eat tonight?
今日の夜何食べようかなって
It's hot, isn't it?
暑いんだよね
I'll spread it out.
広げるよ
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くない?
Ten-chan's first surgery membrane is cut at the bottom.
てんちゃんの初術膜は下が切れてるんだね
The first time I did it, this guy cut his bottom.
初めてやったこと、この人が下を切ったんだよね
Blood comes out from here.
ここから血が出るんですよ
That's right.
そうなんですよ
Is it a good learning experience?
いい勉強になります?
All are good.
どれもいいですね
It's small at times like this.
こういうとき小さいね
It just doesn't come out at all.
全然出てこないんだけど
Oh, is it small?
あ、小さいんですか?
Yeah.
うん
It doesn't hide at all and doesn't come out.
全然隠れて出てこないですよ
Come out, come out.
出ておいで、出ておいで
Let's hold out our hands at the bottom.
下の方、手を出しておこう
Is there something at the bottom?
下の方にあんの?
lie?
嘘?
This is absolutely wrong.
絶対間違ってるよ、これ
Come out.
出ておいで
Oh, this is really small.
あ、これ本当にすごい小っちゃい
It's so small it's scary.
ビビるぐらい小っちゃい
Hello, hello.
こんにちは、こんにちは
Please put your dick in me.
おちんぽいれてください
Show me.
お 見せ
Are you going to show me?
お見せなの?
Are you standing on the earth like that?
あんな地球に立てちゃってる?
Are you making a face?
顔してるの?
Have you gone?
お前行っちゃったの?
Show me, show me.
見せてごらん、見せてごらん
Did you go?
行ったの?
Are you surprised?
びっくりしてる?
I stung hard, and this is it.
ガカガカ刺しちゃって、これ
Shikku, this is bing, this is.
しっくび、これビンビンだよ、これ
Are you excited?
興奮してんの?
Well then, let's get a little closer.
じゃあ、もうちょっと近づこうか
Ah, that's cute.
あ、かわいい
21 years old and like this.
21歳とこんな
Is it okay to have a picture like this?
こんな絵面あっていいんですか?
That's amazing.
すごいね
Impossible?
無理?
Think of me as your boyfriend.
俺のこと、彼氏だと思って
This rash is no good.
こっちのしっくび、ダメでは
This way.
こっち
Please touch.
触ってください
That's right, please lick my little chin.
そっか、ちっくびを舐めてください
Please lick the small part to one side.
片方まで、ちっくびを舐めてください
It's gotten bigger.
大きくなっちゃった
Let it flow.
流して
Be kind, be kind.
優しくね、優しくね
Okay.
いいよ
Please make your little one bigger.
いっぱい、ちっくびを大きくしてね
Where did you learn this?
どこで学んだろう、これ
I wonder where you learned it, it's really interesting.
どこで学んだろう、めちゃくちゃ面白い
Is it YouTube?
YouTubeですか?
See?
ほらね
That means lots of car washes.
いっぱい洗車ってことでね
Like licking soft serve ice cream,
ソフトクリームを舐めるみたいに、
I hope you will be treated well.
ペロッとされてもらおうね
Why don't you sit down and eat banana soft serve?
座ってバナナソフト食べれば?
Come back.
帰ってこら
You have a wide tongue.
舌が広いね
I'm already tired.
もう、疲れちゃった
Can I fall asleep?
寝ちゃっていい?
Can you hold your legs?
足持てる?
Nice, nice.
いい ね、いいね
Have legs.
足持ってて
Hold your legs.
足持っててね
It's in the customer's penis.
お客さんのおちんちに入ってるよ
Let's take the picture myself.
拙者で撮ろうね
Ken-chan's face.
けんちゃんの顔がね
I'll go with you.
お手で向かうから
That 21 year old.
その21歳
Even if I put it away.
しまっても
happy?
嬉しい?
happy.
嬉しい
It would be better to make the old man feel better,
おじさんを気持ちよくしたほうが、
Because you can get money
お金もらえるから
hey.
ね
Equipment, equipment.
器 材やろ、器材
Very good.
すごい良い
I'm trying to make you feel good.
気持ちよくさせようとしてる
I think I'll get tired once.
一旦疲れると思うから
Because I think it's tiring.
疲れると思うから
Your waist.
お腰って
That's amazing.
すごいね
I'm writing something.
何か書いてますよ
She's an amazing masseuse.
すごいマッサージ師だね
I might have a slightly stiffer posture next time, but
次はちょっときつい姿勢かもしれないけど、
It'll help you.
足立てるじゃん
Can you please put your feet up and put your hands behind me?
足立てて、 で ね、後ろに手をついてもらっていい?
Yeah, yeah, that's what it is.
そうそうそう、そういうことそういうこと
yes.
そう
It's a little tight, please go up a little more.
ちょっときついよね、もうちょっと上がってね
A very erotic face.
すごいエロい顔
No, I have to do it first.
いやー、最初にしなきゃいけない
Come here, come here.
こっちおいで、こっちおいで
Standing still, yes.
足立たんで、 そう
Do you stand and put your hands on me?
足立たんで、 こっちに手をつける?
Push your hand or come here.
手を押すか、こっちに
I want you to help me, is this it?
手 ついてほしくて、 これのかな?
Please move.
動いてくれ
The entrance is super narrow.
入口が超狭いね
Is it okay?
大丈夫かな?
Okay, okay.
よしよしよし
Tremble, this person.
震えろ、この人
Shall I just stand on my feet?
足立てばっかりやろうか
Okay, okay.
よしよしよし
Like looking into a camera.
カメラに眺めるようにさ
You can handle it.
手ついていいよ
Good luck and look at the camera.
頑張って、カメラ見てね
Yeah, yeah, nice, nice.
そうそうそう、いいねいいね
Okay, okay.
よしよし
I wish I could wake up again.
もう一回体起こせればいい
You can handle it.
手ついていいよ
Can you wake up?
体起こせる?
Can you raise your legs a little?
足もちょっと起こせる?
Just like that, just like that.
そのままよ、そのまま
Just like that.
そのままそのまま
Well then, put your face on the bed.
じゃあ、顔さ、ベッドにつけちゃって
I can see your butt hole.
お尻の穴丸見える
Can you open my butthole with both hands?
両手でさ、お尻の穴ひよげる?
Oh yeah, the bed.
そうそうそう、ベッド
Oh, I farted.
あ、おならした
different?
違う?
Well then, just wake up.
じゃあ、体起こしてくればいい
Ten-chan, do you like raw cock?
てんちゃんはさ、生チンポが好きなの?
Do you like it?
好きなの?
A raw cock.
生チンポが
Don't you like kobchinpo?
コブチンポは嫌なの?
Do you not like it?
嫌なの?
Do you like it when even your butt is covered by your proud mark?
自慢のマークでお尻さえ隠されるのが好きなの?
Do you like being watched inside?
中凝らされるのが好きなの?
like.
好き
I like hot Sacy.
熱いセイシーが好きなの
like.
好き
Please give me a moment.
ちょっとお願いしますね
Please tell me please let me mess with you.
czyćくびいじらせてくださいって言ってください
Please let me play around with the number one.
番ぱいをいじらせてください
Please tell me to let out as much as I can.
ちくびいじるのはいっぱい出してくださいって言ってください
Please let me know if you are playing around with your breasts.
番ぱいをいじるのかいっぱい出してください
Please give me a hot one instead of a lukewarm one.
ぬるいセイシーでなくて熱いのくださいって
sorry.
すみません
I don't like lukewarm stillness.
ぬるい静止は嫌ですって
ぬ るい静止は嫌です
Please tell me to cum in my pussy.
絶対私のマンコに出してくださいって言ってください
Please cum in my pussy.
絶対私のマンコに出してください
I don't care what you would do if your parents saw you.
親見てたらどうするからもいいよ
terrible?
やばい?
terrible.
やばい
I'm going to cum inside you, so watch me cum inside you.
これから中出ししてあげるから、中出ししているところを見て
please.
ください
Please tell me to watch you cum inside me.
中 出しされるところを見てくださいって言ってください
Inside.
中に
Please tell me to cum inside you.
中に出してくださいって言ってください
Please take it inside.
中に出してください
Please tell me how much you love being creampied.
中出しされるの大好きなのって言ってください
I love being creampied.
中出しされるの大好き
Please tell me you're a perverted woman.
変態女なのって言ってください
She's a perverted woman.
変態女なの
Please let me touch your neck too.
やっちくびもいじらせてくださいって言ってください
やっちくびもいじらせてください
Okay.
いいよ
Please tell me please come inside me.
絶対中に出してくださいって言ってください
Please take it inside.
絶対中に出してください
Mom, please say I'm sorry.
お母さん、ごめんなさいって言ってください
Mom, I'm sorry.
お母さん、ごめんなさい
I love being played with.
仲に出されるの大好きだなって
I love being taken out.
仲に出されるの大好き
Let's go!
行くぞー!
Can you have legs?
足を持てる?
Oh yeah, good.
そうそう、いい
It may be a little harsh, but
ちょっときついかもしれないけど、
good luck.
頑張ってね
You can turn your face a little more sideways.
顔さ、もうちょい横って出せる
thank you for your hard work.
お疲れ様です
It felt good.
気持ちよかった
A lot came out.
い っぱい出ちゃって
Do you put pressure on your butthole?
お尻の穴に力入れる?
Like, like, good
いいね、いいね、いい
hey.
ね
Now, the hand that holds the back leg and the hand that holds it apart.
じゃあ、 あと足を持ってる手、離しておく手
Can you spread your pussy?
おまんこ広げれるかな?
It's a disaster.
大惨事だ
Very low.
すごい低い
Good, good
よ いしょ、よい
Sho.
しょ
See you then.
じゃあ ね
bye bye.
バイバイ
Yes, tension.
はい、テンション
I went inside.
中に出ちゃった
Shall I put it in the camera?
カメラ中に入れてみようか
I want to go a little deeper.
ちょっと奥に行きたいです
Can you go?
行ける?
Go to your limits.
限界まで行ってください
It went in quite a bit.
結構入ったね
Is that the limit?
その限界かな?
Now, slowly move it in and out.
じゃあ、そこにゆっくり出し入れして
You don't have to give it all.
出し切りなくていいから
Take it out and put it back in.
抜いて、また入れて
It's pure white.
真っ白ですよ
This is terrible.
やばいよ
I forgot to mention it for a moment.
ちょっと触れ忘れるよ
It's coming in one by one.
つぼつぼ入ってくるね
That's amazing.
すごいね
The folds are amazing.
ひだがすごいもん
It feels the best.
最気持ちいいわけだ
Well then, let's take it out slowly.
じゃあ、ゆっくり抜いてみようか
Oh my.
あららー
It just came out.
ただ出てきちゃった
See you then.
じゃあね
bye bye.
バイバイ
Yes, tension.
はい、テンション
I went inside.
中に出ちゃった
sorry.
ごめん
Shall I put it in the camera?
カメラ中に入れてみようか
I want to go a little deeper.
ちょっと奥に行きたいです
limit?
限界?
Can you go?
行ける?
Go to your limits.
限界まで行ってください
It went in quite a bit.
結構入ったね
There isn't much in there.
結構入ってない
Is that the limit?
その限界かな?
Then, slowly move it in and out.
じゃあ、そこでゆっくり出し入れして
Put it in and take it out.
出し入れして
You don't have to give it all.
出し切りなくていいから
Take it out and put it back in.
抜いて、また入れて
Yes, yes, yes.
はい はいはい
It's pure white.
真っ白ですよ
This is terrible.
やばいよ
I forgot to mention it for a moment.
ちょっと触れ忘れるよ
It's coming in one by one.
つぼつぼ入ってくるね
amazing
すごい
hey.
ね
Hida is amazing.
ひ だがすごいもん
Well, it feels good.
さ あ、気持ちいいわけだ
Let's take it out slowly.
ゆっくり抜いてみようか
Oh my.
あららー
It came out.
出てきちゃった
See you then.
じゃあね
bye bye.
バイバイ